Guide to the Kristine Stiles Collection, 1900-[ongoing] RL.01254
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Photographs, 7 boxes
  - Family photographs, including 2 albums (Box 172)
  - Family tree list (Box 172)
- Stiles Writings, Art, and Projects, 11 boxes
  Dating from Stiles' Master's thesis in 1976 to recent speeches and articles, this series includes a wide range of materials created or produced by Stiles. Includes her unpublished dissertation on DIAS. Formats include essays, interviews, applications, resumes, and scrapbooks.
  - Dissertation (unpublished): The Destruction in Art Symposium (DIAS): The Radical Cultural Project of Event-Structured Live Art, 1987 (4 folders) (Box 120)
  - M.A. in Art History thesis, 1976 (Box 120)
  - Getty archive discussions, 2008 (Box 121)
  - UC Press (Box 121)
  - Duke Press (Box 121)
  - Franklin Humanities Institute (Box 121)
  - Miscellaneous essays and speeches, 1980s-2000s (Box 121)
  - Drafts, notes, and essays from scholarship and research (6 folders) (Box 121)
  - Kristine Stiles art work; notes and correspondence from the John Latham interview, including Robin Page and Al Hansen, 1980 (Box 122)
  - Wolf Vostell interview, 1982 (Box 122)
  - Museum der Ver Botenen Konst (Box 122)
  - Romeo Drawing Book, artist book by Kristine Stiles (3 folders) (Box 122)
  - WPA project correspondence, 1999 (Box 122)
  - Statements from selling art pieces (Box 122)
  - Sketches, loose art pages (Box 122)
  - Art shows, exhibits, and promotional materials (Box 122)
  - General Practioner stamp, including a rubber stamp, 1980-1981 (Box 122)
  - Yves Tanguy slide show and unused slides (Box 123)
  - Daily calendars, 1985-1986 (Box 123)
  - Clippings about gallery shows (Box 123)
  - Articles and clippings about Stiles (Box 123)
  - International Promotion of Modern Arts Limberg, 1989 (Box 123)
  - Artwork by Stiles, 1967-1978 (Box 123)
  - Art Institute Annual, 1979 (Box 123)
  - Vostell's book, 1983 (Box 123)
  - Artwork by Stiles, 1980s (Box 124)
  - UNC Chapel Hill, 1989 (Box 124)
  - Reviews and writings about Stiles' art (Box 124)
  - Intermedia Arts, 1990 (Box 125)
  - Duke exhibition, 1990 (Box 125)
  - Artwork by Stiles, 1990s (Box 125)
  - Symposium on Racial and Gender Stereotyping, Spelman College, 1990 (Box 125)
  - Questions, 1977-1982 (2 folders) (Box 125)
  - 5 canvas boards (Box 125)
  - The Amazing Adventures of Ray Redford Jameson (Box 125)
  - Looking for America: Questions (includes scrapbooks with newspaper clippings, typed transcript notes) (Box 126)
  - Survival=Survival project, 1980 (Box 126)
  - Romeo Drawing Book (Box 127)
  - Ph.D. diploma, 1987 (Box 127)
  - Exhibit binder (Box 127)
  - Kristine Stiles' Vietnam trip and research (Box 169)
  - Vietnamese books and artwork, collected by Stiles (Box 101)
  - Photographs and notes from visits to Romania, 1993-2002 (Box 169)
  - Press coverage of Stiles, 1990s (Box 203)
  - Miscellaneous photographs and artwork (Box 203)
  - "She Is" print, 1983 (Box 203)
  - Robert Rauschenberg Exhibition, 2014 (Box 214)
  - European Cultural Foundation, Princess Margriet Award (Box 215)
  - Robert Rauschenberg Exhibition (Box 215)
  - European Cultural Foundation: Princess Margriet Award (Box 215)
- Printed Materials, 5 boxes
  Includes issues of journals, magazines, newsletters, and zines that Stiles collected. Many were only published once or twice. Also includes 1 box of exhibition brochures from the DIA Center for the Arts and Apexart.org publications from 1996-2012. These have been organized chronologically.
  - Apexart.org publications, 1996-2015 (Box 99)
    - Ceremonial, curated by Barry Schwabsky, October 24-November 23, 1996. (Box 99)
    - Colorflex, curated buy Raphael Rubinstein, 1997 (Box 99)
    - Color Detour, curated by Faye Hirsch, January 9-February 8, 1997. (Box 99)
    - SLAD, curated by Mary Jones and Janice Krasnow, February 13-March 15, 1997. (Box 99)
    - Ornament and Landscape: On the Nature of Artifice, curated by Tom Huhn, March 20-April 19, 1997. (Box 99)
    - 444, curated by Paul Ha, Stefano Basilico, Jessica Fredericks and Andrew Freiser, and Lisa Spellman, July 9-August 2, 1997. (Box 99)
    - Dazzle Gradually, curated by Gregory Volk, September 11-October 11, 1997. (Box 99)
    - 'Pagan' Stories: The Situations of Narrative in Recent Art, curated by Janet Kraynak, October 16-November 15, 1997. (Box 99)
    - Try A Little Tenderness, curated by Joe Fyfe, November 26-January 4, 1997. (Box 99)
    - Apex Art C.P. Studio Program, curatored by Isabella Prata, Lars Grambye, Young-Chul Lee, Olesya Turkina, Peter Birmingham, 1997-1998. (Box 99)
    - Original Scale, curated by John Yau, January 7-February 1998. (Box 99)
    - The Sound of One Hand: The collection of Collier Schorr, March 19-April 18, 1998. (Box 99)
    - Scattered Affinities, curated by Nuria Enguita Mayo, April 23-May 23, 1998. (Box 99)
    - Live and let die, curated by Udo Kittelmann, June 4-20, 1998. (Box 99)
    - Four Curators Four Artists Four Weeks, curated by Casey Kaplan, Hudson, Marc Pottier, Klaus Biesenbach, June 24-Muly 22, 1998. (Box 99)
    - Remembering Times Past, curated by Irena Popiashvili, September 9-October 10, 1998. (Box 99)
    - Finger, curated by Joseph Kosuth, October 22-November 14, 1998. (Box 99)
    - Harriet Craig, curated by David Rimanelli, November 19-December 19, 1998. (Box 99)
    - Deep Skin Exirsions: Eary Work by Howard Fried, curated by Dennis Oppenheim, November 20-January 3, 1998. (Box 99)
    - Avoiding Objects, curated by Alice Smits, January 8-February 6, 1999. (Box 99)
    - Actual Size, curated by Nancy Princenthal, February 11-March 13, 1999. (Box 99)
    - Mixology: An Installation by Christine Siemens, essay by Dave Hickey, March 18-April 17, 1999. (Box 99)
    - Street Theater: An installation by Yung Ho Chang and Atelier FCJZ, curated by Hou Hanru &Evelyne Jouanno, April 22-May22, 1999. (Box 99)
    - Arrested Ambition, curated by Gregory Williams, May 27-June 26, 1999. (Box 99)
    - 444, curated by Spencer Brownstone, Susan Harris, Carol Greene, Christian Haye, June 1999. (Box 99)
    - Building Histories, curated by Maureen Connor, October 14-November 13, 1999. (Box 99)
    - The Production of Production, curated by Tim Griffin &Bennett Simpson, September 9-October 9, 1999. (Box 99)
    - Cancelled, Ingrid Schaffner, Dorothy Krasowska, Carolee Thea, David Robbins, November 18-December 18, 1999. (Box 99)
    - Double Space, curated by A.S. Bessa, January 6-February 5, 2000. (Box 99)
    - Chispa, curated by Luis Jiminenz, February 9-March 11, 2000. (Box 99)
    - Insertion: Self and Other, curated by Salah M. Hassan, April 18-May 20, 2000. (Box 99)
    - Context, curated by José Roca, May 24-June 24, 2000. (Box 99)
    - 222 two curators two artists two weeks, curated by Magdalena Sawon and Jeanne Greenberg Rohatyn, June 28-July 8 &July 12-July 22, 2000. (Box 99)
    - Errant Gestures: Visual and Verbal Correspondences, curated by Susett Min, September 7-October 8, 2000. (Box 99)
    - Chinese Whispers, curated by Branka Stipancic and Ana Devic, October 11-November 11, 2000. (Box 99)
    - Something Happened, curated by Sally Berger, November 15-December 16, 2000. (Box 99)
    - Making the Making, curated by Charles Goldman, January5-February 3, 2001. (Box 99)
    - Demonstration Room: Ideal House, curated by Jesús Fuenmayor and Julieta González, February 7-March 10, 2001. (Box 99)
    - In/SITE/Out: Inquiries into Social Space, curated by Karen E. Jones, March 16-April 14, 2001. (Box 99)
    - Gesture, Posture and Bad Attitude in Contemporary News Photography, curated by David Byrne, April 18-May 19, 2001. (Box 99)
    - Lost and Found. curated by René Block, May 23-June 23, 2001. (Box 99)
    - 222 two curators two artists two weeks, curated by Derek Eller and Annie Herron and Larry Walczak, June 27-July 14 and July 18-July 28, 2001. (Box 99)
    - SportCult, curated by Eurdice Arratia, September 7-November 3, 2001. (Box 99)
    - Revolving Doors, curated by Montse Badia, November 14-December 22, 2001. (Box 99)
    - Apexart Year End Report, 2001. (Box 99)
    - Letter to Supporters, from Steven Rand, Editor of apexart, and his and administrative staff, December 6, 2001. (Box 99)
    - Gain, curated by Kelly Taxter, January 4-26, 2002. (Box 99)
    - Unjustified, curated by Kerry James Marshall, January 30-March 2, 2002. (Box 99)
    - Art That Heals, curated by Jean-Hubert Martin, March 6-April 6, 2002. (Box 99)
    - The Passions of the Good Citizen, curated by Heather Felty, April 10-May 11, 2002. (Box 99)
    - Public Key, curated by Angeline Scherf, May 15-June 15, 2002. (Box 99)
    - Stardust, selected by Anton Kern, June 21-July 10, 2002. (Box 99)
    - Time is free, curated by Jan Hoet with Ann Demeester, October 9-November 9, 2002. (Box 99)
    - Sans an exhibition, November-December 2002. (Box 99)
    - Apexart Season End Report, 2002/2003. (Box 99)
    - Walking in the City, curated by Melissa Brookhart Beyer &Jill Dawsey, January 4-February 1, 2003. (Box 99)
    - An Interest in Life, curated by John Baldessari and Meg Cranston, February 5-March 8, 2003. (Box 99)
    - Between the Lines, curated by Rebecca Gordon Nesbitt, March 15-April 12, 2003. (Box 99)
    - Undesire, curated by Vasif Kortun, April 18-May 17, 2003. (Box 99)
    - Art After the Age of Mechanical Reproduction, curated by Eugenie Tsai, May 21- June 21, 2003. (Box 99)
    - Summer Program, curated by Katy Siegel, 2003 (Box 99)
    - To Be Political It Has To Look Nice, curated by Pablo León Barra, October 11-November 8, 2003. (Box 99)
    - Looking Awry, Maja Bajevic, Igor Grubic, Aydan Murteaoglu, Adrian PACI, November 12-December 12, 2003. (Box 99)
    - Apexart Season End Report, 2003/2004. (Box 99)
    - Adaptations, curated by Craig Buckley, January 7-February 7, 2004. (Box 99)
    - Treasure Maps, curated by Janine Antoni, February 11-March 13, 2004. (Box 99)
    - The Future of the Reciprocal Readymade (The use-value of art), curated by Stephen Wright, March 14-April 17, 2004. (Box 99)
    - Black Dragon Society: Jedediah Caesar, Steve Canaday, Gerald Davis, Jacques de Beaufort, Mark Galamco, Hannah Greely, Nick Lowe, Jodies Mohr, Ry Rocklen, Oscar Santas, Rob Thom, April 21-May 22, 2004. (Box 99)
    - O.K., America!, curated by Peter Noever, May 26-June 26, 2004. (Box 99)
    - Apexart Calendar, Fall 2004. (Box 99)
    - Building the Unthinkable: Constructing Destruction, curated by Christian Stayner, September 8-Octobr 9, 2004. (Box 99)
    - Place for the Self, curated by Amnon Barzel, October 13-November 13, 2004. (Box 99)
    - Drafting Deceit, curated by Oksana Pasaiko, November 3, 2004. (Box 99)
    - Apexart Season End Report, 2004/2005. (Box 99)
    - Apexart Calendar, Winter 2005. (Box 99)
    - Too Much Pollution to Demonstrate: Soft Guerrillas in Tehran's Contemporary Art Scene, curated by Amiel Grumberg, January 5-February 9, 2005. (Box 99)
    - Maurizio Couldn't Be Here, curated by Steven Rand, Kari Conte, Heather Kouris, and Fernanda Arruda (who was invited by Maurizio Cattelan), February 12-March 12, 2005. (Box 99)
    - Social Democracy Revisited, curated by Jonas Ekeberg, March 16-April 16, 2005. (Box 99)
    - Afterall, curated by Charles Esche, April 27-May 21, 2005. (Box 99)
    - Sacred Wild: Opening to Shakti, curated by Suzi Gablik, May 25- June 25, 2006. (Box 99)
    - Philosophical Toys, curated by Sina Najafi, June 29-July 30, 2005. (Box 99)
    - If It's Too Bad to be True, It Could Be DISNFORMATION, curated by Mercedes Vicente, October 19-Novemer 26, 2005. (Box 99)
    - The Last Generation, curated by Max Henry, November 30-January 7, 2006. (Box 99)
    - One Brief Moment, curated by Mark Soo, January 11-February 18, 2006. (Box 99)
    - Neo-Sincerity: The Difference Between the Comic and the Cosmic is a Single Letter, curated by Amei Wallach, February 22-April 8, 2006. (Box 99)
    - Re_dis_trans: Voltage of Relocation and Displacement, curated by Aniko Erdosi (Box 99)
    - May 24-July 1, 2006: Sweet Taboos: A Mini Tirana Biennale in New York, curated by Edi Muka, April 12-May 20, 2006. (Box 99)
    - Gifts go in one direction, organized by Alexander Nagel (Box 99)
    - September 6-October 14, 2006: neo-con. Contemporary Returns to Conceptual Art, curated by Cristiana Perrella, July 5-August 12, 2006. (Box 99)
    - The Universe in a Handkerchief, presented by Gallery Yujiro, curated by Anthony Spira and James Smith, October 6-November 18, 2006. (Box 99)
    - Apexart Season End Report, 2005/2006. (Box 99)
    - Let Everything Be Temporary, or When is the Exhibition?, curated by Elena Filipovic, January 10-February 17, 2007. (Box 99)
    - Q.P.M.A.F. (Quick! Pull My Animated Finger!), Matt Silverstein &Dave Jeser, February 24-April 14, 2007. (Box 99)
    - The Museum of Crime and Museum of God, curated by Luc Sante, May 16-June 23, 2007. (Box 99)
    - The Most Curatorial Biennial of the Universe, July 7-August 11, 2007. (Box 99)
    - Stalking with Stories: The Pioneers of the Immemorable, curated by Antonia Majaca and Ivana Bago, September 19-November 3, 2007. (Box 99)
    - Land Grab - Strategies of Occupation: Grabbing Land and The Political Agency of The Artist, curated by Sarah Lookofsky and Lillian Fellman, November 9-November 30, 2007. (Box 99)
    - Apex art Season End Brochure, 2006/2007. (Box 99)
    - Your Vote Counts!: The (Self) Promotion TV Project, guest essay by Carlo McCormick, January 9-February 16, 2008. (Box 99)
    - Boris Groys: Thinking in Loop, essay by Boris Groys, February 20-March 29, 2008. (Box 99)
    - Lots of Things Like This, curated by Dave Eggers, April 2-May 10, 2008. (Box 99)
    - Nessie Does New York: Monetizing Myth, Legend, Culture, essay by Chris A. Kenny, July 2-August2, 2008. (Box 99)
    - Scrawl, essay by Harley Spiller, September 4-October 11, 2008. (Box 99)
    - Perverted by Theater, curated by Franklin Evans and Paul David Young, October 22-December 6, 2008. (Box 99)
    - Nameless Science, essay by Henk Slager, December 10-January 31, 2009. (Box 99)
    - Apexart Residency Program Brochure, 2007/2008. (Box 99)
    - I Am Art: An Expression of the Visual &Artistic Process of Plastic Surgery, curated by Anthony Berlet, M.D., March 28-May 9, 2009. (Box 99)
    - X,Y, Z and U, curated by The League of Imaginary Scientists (a Los Angeles-based collective specializing in Pataphysics, Interactive Art, and Art/Science Collaborations. The League was founded in 2006. The principal members are: Dr. Hernandez-Gomez (Lucy HG, Dr. Stephan Schleidan (Steve Shoffner, Prof. William T. Madmann (Jeremy Speed Schwartz), Prof. J. Johansen (Matt Solomon), Prof. Troubadour (Leonard Trubia), June 4-July 3, 2009. (Box 99)
    - Wondermare, curated by Susan McIntosh and Albert Wilking, July 8-August8, 2009. (Box 99)
    - A Way Beyond Fashion, curated by Robert Punkenhofer, September 16-October 24, 2009. (Box 99)
    - The Incidental Person, curated by Antony Hudek, January 6-February 20, 2010. (Box 99)
    - Don't Piss on Me and Tell Me It's Raining, Richard Holland and Duncan MacKenzie, April 7-May 22, 2010. (Box 99)
    - Free Size, curated by Logan Bay, March 13-April 17, 2010. (Box 99)
    - Change the Channel: WCVB-TV 1972-1982, curated by Gary Fogelson &Michael Hutcherson, January 12-March 5, 2011. (Box 99)
    - Washed Out, curated by Corina Oprea, Isabel Löfgren, Judith Souriau, Milena Placentile, and Valerio Del Baglivo, February 2-March 3, 2011. (Box 99)
    - We Have Woven the Motherlands With Nets of Iron, curated by Eric Gottesman and Toleen Touq, May 4-June 4, 2011. (Box 99)
    - The Peripheterists, curated by Jocko Weyland, June 1-July 30, 2011. (Box 99)
    - Consent, curated by Lynsey G., March 21-May 12, 2012. (Box 99)
    - The Permanent Way, organized by Brian Sholis, June 6-July 28, 2012. (Box 99)
    - Private Matters, organized by Ceren Erdem, Jaime Schwartz, and Lisa Hayes Williams, January 16-March 1, 2014. (Box 212)
    - UHF42, organized by Mike Crane, May 29-June 27, 2014. (Box 212)
    - Ecologia del Techo de Lima, organized by Carlos Leon-Xijimenez, Nov. 3-Dec. 1, 2012 (Box 212)
    - Laughter, organized by Kari Cwynar, May 23-July 27, 2013 (Box 212)
    - Memphis Social, organized by Tom McGlynn, May 10-18, 2013 (Box 212)
    - Coding the Body, organized by Leah Buechley, March 20-May 10, 2014 (Box 212)
    - UNREST: Revolt Against Reason, organized by Natalie Musteata, Sept. 12-Oct. 27, 2012 (Box 212)
    - Scaryoke, organized by Dan Kois, Nov. 7-Dec. 21, 2013 (Box 212)
    - Heterotopia, re: Marfa, Oct. 5-Nov. 2, 2013 (Box 212)
    - As Real as it Gets, organized by Rob Walker, Nov. 15-Dec. 22, 2012 (Box 212)
    - Death of a Cameraman, organized by Martin Waldmeier, Sept. 13-Oct. 26, 2013 (Box 212)
    - The Art of 9/11, curated by Arthur C. Danto, Sept. 7-Oct. 15, 2005 (Box 212)
    - Open Sesame, organized by Ola El-Khalidi, Jan. 17-Mar. 2, 2013 (Box 212)
    - Exhibition Space, organized by Greg Allen, Mar. 21-May 8, 2013 (Box 212)
  - DIA Center for the Arts brochures, 1991-2004 (Box 99)
    - Lawrence Weiner: Displacement. New York: DIA Center for the Arts, April 1991-April 1992. (Box 99)
    - Robert Gober. New York: DIA Center for the Arts, September 24, 1992-June 20, 1993. (Box 99)
    - On Kawara: One Thousand Days One Million Years. New York: DIA Center for the Arts, January 1-December 31, 1993. (Box 99)
    - Joseph Beuys: 7000 Oaks. Long-term installation on West 22nd Street between 10th and 11th Avenues New York City. New York: DIA Center for the Arts, 1988-present. (Box 99)
    - Andy Warhol: The Last Supper. New York: DIA Center for the Arts, September 16, 1994-June 25, 1995. (Box 99)
    - Alighiero E. Boetti and Frédéric Bruly Bouabré: Worlds Envisioned. New York: DIA Center for the Arts, October 6, 1994-June 25, 1995 (Box 99)
    - James Coleman: Projected Images: 1972-1994. New York: DIA Center for the Arts, April 14-March 12, 1995. (Box 99)
    - Gerhard Richter: Atlas. New York: DIA Center for the Arts, April 27, 1995-Spring 1996. (Box 99)
    - Jessica Stockholder: Your Skin in this Weather Bourne Eye-Threads & Swollen Perfume. New York: DIA Center for the Arts, October 5, 1995-June 23, 1996. (Box 99)
    - Hanne Darboven; Kulturgeschichte 1880-1983, 1980-83. New York: DIA Center for the Arts, March 28, 1996-June 1, 1997. (Box 99)
    - Juan Muñoz: A Place Called Abroad. New York: DIA Center for the Arts, September 26, 1996-June 29, 1997. (Box 99)
    - Dan Flavin: (1962/63, 1970, 1996). New York: DIA Center for the Arts, May 22, 1997-June 14, 1998. (Box 99)
    - Robert Irwin: Part I: Prologue: x 183; Part II: Excursus: Homage to the Square3. New York: DIA Center for the Arts, September 13, 1998-June 13, 1999. (Box 99)
    - Thomas Schütte: Gloria in Memoria. New York: DIA Center for the Arts, February 4-June 13, 1999. (Box 99)
    - Stan Douglas and Douglas Gordon: Double Vision. New York: DIA Center for the Arts, February 11, 1999-February 2000. (Box 99)
    - Bridget Riley: Reconnaissance. New York: DIA Center for the Arts, September 21, 2000-June 17, 2001. (Box 99)
    - Panamarenko: Orbit. New York: DIA Center for the Arts, November 29, 2000-June 17, 2001. (Box 99)
    - Diana Thater: Knots + Surfaces. New York: DIA Center for the Arts, January 24, 2001-January 2002. (Box 99)
    - Jorge Pardo and Gilberto Zorio: Reverb. New York: DIA Center for the Arts, September 19, 2001-June 16, 2002. (Box 99)
    - Alfred Jensen: Concordance. New York: DIA Center for the Arts, September 20, 2001-June 16, 2002. (Box 99)
    - Roni Horn. New York: DIA Center for the Arts, Part I: October 17, 2001-February 17, 2002; Part II: February 27-June 16, 2002. (Box 99)
    - Dan Graham: Rooftop Urban Park Project long-term installation. New York: DIA Center for the Arts, September 12, 1991 - January 11, 2004 (Box 99)
  - Regular and oversize journals and magazines (Box 127-130)
  - "Von muri si vom fi liberi," Bucharest: Editura Meridiane, 1990 (Box 212)
    Romanian Revolution book.
  - "Fallout Protection: What to Know and Do about Nuclear Attack," U.S. Dept. of Defense, 1961 (Box 212)
  - Calendar from Nicaragua, 1995 (Box 212)
- Name files, 42 boxes
  Stiles created these files to sort her correspondence between colleagues, friends, and family, as well as small amounts of material from various artists. These files have been arranged alphabetically.
  - Abe, Stan (Box 100)
  - Abramovic, Marina, 1998-2008 (Box 100)
  - Acconci, Vito, 1980-1992 (Box 100)
  - Adams, Bobby Neel, 1996 (Box 100)
  - Adams, Dennis (Box 100)
  - Adilogly, Maureen (Box 100)
  - Adriasola, Ignacio, 2011 (Box 100)
  - "The Aesthetics of Risk," Getty Center, 2006 (Box 100)
  - Agalidi, Sanda, 1993 (Box 100)
  - Ágnes, Szanyi, 2009 (Box 100)
  - Ahearn, John, 1992 (Box 100)
  - Aichele, K. Porter, 2003 (Box 100)
  - Aitken, Doug, 2002 (Box 100)
  - Akwari, Anne, 1999 (Box 100)
  - Alberro, Alex, 1997 (Box 100)
  - Aldrich, Diane, 1999 (Box 100)
  - Alexander, Cheryl, 1999 (Box 100)
  - Alexander, Darsie, 2006 (Box 100)
  - Allen, Jessee (Box 100)
  - Altieri, Charles, 1997 (Box 100)
  - Alys, Francis (Box 214)
  - Ambrosius, Gerold, 1979 (Box 100)
  - Amos, Emma, 2006 (Box 100)
  - Andersen, Eric, 1982-1997 (Box 100)
  - Andersen, Wayne, 1997 (Box 100)
  - Anderson, Jim (Box 100)
  - Anderson, Katie, 2008 (Box 100)
  - Anderson, Kristin, 2007 (Box 100)
  - Anderson, Laurie, 1979-2008 (Box 100)
  - Anderson, Simon, 1993 (Box 100)
  - Anderson, T.J., 2000-2012 (Box 100, Box 214)
  - Anderson-Spivy, Alexandra, 1994 (Box 100)
  - Andre, Carl, 1997 (Box 100)
  - Andree-Trembley, Julie, 2002 (Box 100)
  - Andrews, Kathryn, 1998-2003, 2015 (Box 100, Box 214)
  - Anglim, Paule, 1998 (Box 100)
  - Anker, Suzanne, 1992-2000 (Box 100)
  - Antik, Alexandru (Box 100)
  - Antin, Eleanor, 1996 (Box 100)
  - Antliff, Mark, 1997-2008 (Box 100)
  - Antoni, Janine, 1997 (Box 100)
  - Apóstol, Alexander (Box 100)
  - Apostol, Corina Lucia, 2005-2009 (Box 100)
  - Apple, Jacki, 2000-2001 (Box 131)
  - Apte, Mahadev L., 1992 (Box 131)
  - Aravamudah, Srinivas, 2006-2009 (Box 131)
  - ARCH, 1998 (Box 131)
  - Archiv X, 1998 (Box 131)
  - Ariail, Kate Dobbs, 1994 (Box 131)
  - Armacost, J. Andrew, 2011 (Box 131)
  - Armstrong, Liz, 1983-2008 (2 folders) (Box 131)
  - Arnold, Mark, 1984 (Box 131)
  - Arocena, Catalina, 1995 (Box 131)
  - Ars Electronica, 1991-1999 (Box 131)
  - Arsem, Marilyn, 2006 (Box 131)
  - Art Attack, 1989-1995 (Box 131)
  - Art Guys, 1997-2000 (Box 131)
  - ART-hoc, Moldovia, 1997-2002 (Box 131)
  - Art in General (Box 131)
  - Arta Grafica, 1992 (Box 131)
  - "Artistic Practice and Theory in Modern Art", Goethe University, 2010 (Box 131)
  - ArtPace, 1999 (Box 131)
  - Artpool, 1993-2008 (Box 132)
  - Art-Rite serial, Issue No. 7, 1974 (Box 214)
  - Aschheim, Eve, 1985-2007 (2 folders) (Box 132)
  - Ascott, Roy, 1996 (Box 132)
  - Ash, Elizabethp (Box 132)
  - Ashton Harris, Lyle, 2013 (Box 214)
  - Asquino, Mark L., 1992-1993 (Box 132)
  - Assembling (Box 132)
  - Atkinson, Terry, 1979 (Box 132)
  - Atwater, Skip, 2000 (Box 132)
  - Atzenweiler, Lindy, 1997 (Box 132)
  - Audio Scene '79, 1979 (Box 132)
  - Auman, J. Mack, 1992-1993 (Box 132)
  - Auman, Graham, 1993-2014 (Box 132)
  - AURA, 1975 (Box 132)
  - Averns, Dick, 2006 (Box 132)
  - Avram, Horea (Box 132)
  - Aycock, Alice, 1977 (Box 132)
  - Ay-O, 1996-2001 (Box 132)
  - Azoulay, Ariella, 1994 and undated (Box 132)
  - Baars, Mel, 2004-2005 (Box 132)
  - Babias, Marius, 1996-2008 (Box 132)
  - Backstein, Joseph, 1998 (Box 132)
  - Badovinac, Zdenka, 1997-2001 (Box 132)
  - Bae, Youngji, 2009 (Box 132)
  - Baer, Jo, 1993 (Box 132)
  - Bago, Ivana, 2015 (Box 214)
  - Bailey, Dan, 2000 (Box 132)
  - Bailey, David A., 1998 (Box 132)
  - Baird, Marty, 1994 (Box 132)
  - Baker, Lee D., 2011-2013 (Box 132)
  - Balfour, Ali, 1999 (Box 132)
  - Baldon, Diana, 2008 (Box 132)